Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09
  - Photo Unit #: E0240 Minuto on Motorcycle, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0286)
  - Photo Unit #: E0241 Joseph Brandt, Juan Mena, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0287)
  - Photo Unit #: E0243 Sound track, Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0288)
  - Photo Unit #: E0244 [(?) addressing the troops], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0289)
  - Photo Unit #: E0245 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0290)
  - Photo Unit #: E0246 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0291)
  - Photo Unit #: E0247 Machine-gunners building nests, Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0292)
  - Photo Unit #: E0248 William Susman [alias Bill Ellis], Joseph Brandt, Ivan Rujevcic, Juan Mena, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0293)
  - Photo Unit #: E0249 William Susman [alias Bill Ellis], Joseph Brandt, Ivan Rujevcic, Juan Mena, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0294)
  - Photo Unit #: E0250 Joseph Taylor and Burt Jackson, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0295)
  - Photo Unit #: E0254 Youth delegates address MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0296)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative; Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/60)
  - Photo Unit #: E0255 [Soldier at attention], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0297)
  - Photo Unit #: E0256 [Soldiers at attention], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0298)
  - Photo Unit #: E0258 Trade Union Delegation in April, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0299)
  - Photo Unit #: E0260 [Soldiers, relaxing/smoking], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0300)
  - Photo Unit #: E0261 [Soldiers, relaxing at fortification], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0301)
  - Photo Unit #: E0264 Lieutenant Edwin Bee and topography class, Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0302)
  - Photo Unit #: E0272 First-aid class, Sanidad [Health], undated (Item 11-1470)
  - Photo Unit #: E0273 Dr. Mark Straus and Dr. Imek Bernstein, Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0263)
  - Photo Unit #: E0279 Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0303)
  - Photo Unit #: E0281 Transmiciones [Transmissions], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0304)
  - Photo Unit #: E0282 John Gates, [?] and Milton Wolff, undated (Item 11-1199)
  - Photo Unit #: E0283 Vladimir Copic, David Doran, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0305)
  - Photo Unit #: E0284 Group of soldiers [?], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0306)
  - Photo Unit #: E0285 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0307)
  - Photo Unit #: E0286 [Loading a truck], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0308)
  - Photo Unit #: E0287 [Loading a truck], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0309)
  - Photo Unit #: E0288 [Loading a truck], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0310)
  - Photo Unit #: E0291 [Digging/building fortifications (?)], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0311)
  - Photo Unit #: E0292 [Digging/building fortifications (?)], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0312)
  - Photo Unit #: E0293 [Soldiers, marching], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0313)
  - Photo Unit #: E0294 Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0314)
  - Photo Unit #: E0296 Dressing a wound, Sanidad [Health], undated (Item 11-1471)
  - Photo Unit #: E0297 Lou Ziven, Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0315)
  - Photo Unit #: E0298 Dr. Imek Bernstein, Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0316)
  - Photo Unit #: E0299 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic and [?], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0317)
  - Photo Unit #: E0302 Saul Wellman, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0318)
  - Photo Unit #: E0305 Cubans, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0319)
  - Photo Unit #: E0307 Washing Up, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0320)
  - Photo Unit #: E0308 [14th International Brigade (?)], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0321)
  - Photo Unit #: E0309 [14th International Brigade (?)], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0322)
  - Photo Unit #: E0310 [(?) addressing the troops], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0323)
  - Photo Unit #: E0311 [(?) addressing the troops], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0324)
  - Photo Unit #: E0312 [Three Spanish (?) soldiers], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0325)
  - Photo Unit #: E0314 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Corbera, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0326)
  - Photo Unit #: E0317 Going to the Botaja front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0327)
  - Photo Unit #: E0320 Going to the Botaja front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0328)
  - Photo Unit #: E0325 Captain [?], Ivan Rujevcic, Lieutenant Steve Tsermengas, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0329)
  - Photo Unit #: E0326 Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0330)
  - Photo Unit #: E0328 [Kitchen/cooking; man holding a ladle over a pot of soup], undated (Item 11-1472)
  - Photo Unit #: E0330 Action Shots: Batea, Gandesa, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0331)
  - Photo Unit #: E0333 Some of our tanks at Batea during Fascist offensive, undated (Item 11-1473)
  - Photo Unit #: E0336 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1200)
  - Photo Unit #: E0340 Action Shots: Batea, Gandesa, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0332)
  - Photo Unit #: E0344 Action Shots: Batea, Gandesa, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0333)
  - Photo Unit #: E0345 Soldiers watching Fascist planes, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1474)
  - Photo Unit #: E0347 Miguel Lausurica of Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1475)
  - Photo Unit #: E0348 Group from Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1476)
  - Photo Unit #: E0349 Oficina comrades at Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1477)
  - Photo Unit #: E0351 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1478)
  - Photo Unit #: E0357 Group in Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1479)
  - Photo Unit #: E0358 Auto Park kitchen serves lunch, Mora La Nueva, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0077)
  - Photo Unit #: E0361 Armory at work, Mas Roig, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1480)
  - Photo Unit #: E0364 Comrades of Pagaduria and Intendencia, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1481)
  - Photo Unit #: E0365 Unidentified Soldier in Chair (Item 11-1875)
  - Photo Unit #: E0367 Highway near Mora La Nueva during retreat from Gandesa, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0078)
  - Photo Unit #: E0368 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1482)
  - Photo Unit #: E0369 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa [with cart and flock of sheep], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1483)
  - Photo Unit #: E0370 Highway near Mora la Nueva during retreat from Gandesa [mules under a tree], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1484)
  - Photo Unit #: E0371 Commissariat wall newspaper, Falset, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1485)
  - Photo Unit #: E0372 Auto Park machine shop, Alcover, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1486)
  - Photo Unit #: E0376 British Battalion, Darmos [cook serving men], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1487)
  - Photo Unit #: E0377 [?] and Louis Secundy of Auto Park at Mora La Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0079)
  - Photo Unit #: E0378 Auto Park kitchen serves lunch, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0080)
  - Photo Unit #: E0381 Lunch time in the Auto Park, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0081)
  - Photo Unit #: E0382 Lunch time in the Auto Park, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0082)
  - Photo Unit #: E0383 Louis Secundy, [?], [?], Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1488)
  - Photo Unit #: E0384 Group from the Auto Park, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0083)
  - Photo Unit #: E0385 Group from the Auto Park, Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1489)
  - Photo Unit #: E0387 Frank Arvola, chief cook in Auto Park, Alcover, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0334)
  - Photo Unit #: E0388 Lieutenant [?] Sanchez, Commissar Samuel Gonshak, Lieutenant Louis Secundy, Alcover, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0335)
  - Photo Unit #: E0392 Godfrey Thompson cleaning rifle, Brigade Armory, Falset, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1201)
  - Photo Unit #: E0398 ? talking to James Bourne, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0336)
  - Photo Unit #: E0399 Samuel Gonshak and Solomon Rosenblum [alias Sol Rose], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0380)
  - Photo Unit #: E0402 Coffee at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0337)
  - Photo Unit #: E0403 Brigade staff meeting, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1490)
  - Photo Unit #: E0404 Brigade Office, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0338)
  - Photo Unit #: E0406 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0339)
  - Photo Unit #: E0408 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic confers with staff officers, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0340)
  - Photo Unit #: E0412 James Bourne and Captain Carl Slater, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0341)
  - Photo Unit #: E0414 [Soldier relaxing, Darmos], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0342)
  - Photo Unit #: E0416 Brigade Staff meeting, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0343)
  - Photo Unit #: E0417 Brigade officers meeting, Darmos; Captain David Kami, commander of Sapodores [at right], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1491)
  - Photo Unit #: E0421 José María Varela, Daniel Pasternack [?], Eloy Bouha [?], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0344)
  - Photo Unit #: E0422 Showers in the 15th International Brigade, Falset, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1492)
  - Photo Unit #: E0423 Engineers working on fortifications, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0345)
  - Photo Unit #: E0427 Antonio Garcia, Auto Park, 59th Battalion Miguel Lausurica [?], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0346)
  - Photo Unit #: E0434 [3 men] writing letters home, undated (Item 11-1493)
  - Photo Unit #: E0435 Showers, 15th International Brigade, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0347)
  - Photo Unit #: E0437 Letty Abraham of Bagdad, Mack Coad of Alabama, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0348)
  - Photo Unit #: E0439 Letty Abraham of Bagdad, Mack Coad of Alabama, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0349)
  - Photo Unit #: E0441 David (Red) Drummond, George Watt, William Maher, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0350)
  - Photo Unit #: E0442 Commissars Meeting, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0351)
  - Photo Unit #: E0443 John Weldon, Lincoln-Washington Secretary, and Felix Kuzman, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0352)
  - Photo Unit #: E0445 Card game in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0353)
  - Photo Unit #: E0446 Card game in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1202)
  - Photo Unit #: E0447 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos; [soldiers resting one holding a map], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1494)
  - Photo Unit #: E0448 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion after April 2nd retreat, Darmos; [sitting on ground, drinking wine], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1495)
  - Photo Unit #: E0449 Joe Bianca, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0354)
  - Photo Unit #: E0450 Joe Bianca,cleaning a rifle, and others, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1496)
  - Photo Unit #: E0451 Card game in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0355)
  - Photo Unit #: E0453 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0356)
  - Photo Unit #: E0454 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0357)
  - Photo Unit #: E0455 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0358)
  - Photo Unit #: E0466 Commissariat wall board, Ebro Front, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1497)
  - Photo Unit #: E0467 [Fortification, soldiers at attention], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0359)
  - Photo Unit #: E0468 [Soldiers with truck], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0360)
  - Photo Unit #: E0469 Auto Park group, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0361)
  - Photo Unit #: E0471 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0362)
  - Photo Unit #: E0476 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0363)
  - Photo Unit #: E0480 [Machine-gun nest (?)], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0364)
  - Photo Unit #: E0481 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0365)
  - Photo Unit #: E0482 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0366)
  - Photo Unit #: E0483 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0367)
  - Photo Unit #: E0484 [Soldier in grass hut], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0368)
  - Photo Unit #: E0485 [Machine-gun crew], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0369)
  - Photo Unit #: E0486 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0370)
  - Photo Unit #: E0487 [Soldiers, group], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0371)
  - Photo Unit #: E0488 Band concert, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0372)
  - Photo Unit #: E0490 Band concert, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0373)
  - Photo Unit #: E0491 15th International Brigade band, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1498)
  - Photo Unit #: E0496 Band concert, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0374)
  - Photo Unit #: E0498 Band concert, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0375)
  - Photo Unit #: E0501 Band concert, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0376)
  - Photo Unit #: E0505 Lincoln-Washington [officers?] and Estado Major, undated (Item 11-1499)
  - Photo Unit #: E0506 Lincoln-Washington and Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-1500)
  - Photo Unit #: E0507 Lincoln-Washington and Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-1501)
  - Photo Unit #: E0510 [Soldiers, waiting to eat], undated (Item 11-0377)
  - Photo Unit #: E0511 [Soldiers, relaxing], undated (Item 11-0388)
  - Photo Unit #: E0512 [Preparing fortifications (?)], undated (Item 11-0389)
  - Photo Unit #: E0513 [Automobile], undated (Item 11-0390)
  - Photo Unit #: E0514 Battalion Commissars Robert Cooney, Antonio Gil Cabezas, Frank Rogers, J.M. Varseda, George Watt, Sandor Voros, 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0391)
  - Photo Unit #: E0515 Carl Syvanen, MacKenzie-Papineau, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0392)
  - Photo Unit #: E0517 Max Farrar, cook, Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0393)
  - Photo Unit #: E0521 Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0394)
  - Photo Unit #: E0523 [Soldiers, eating/drinking], May 1938 (Item 11-0395)
  - Photo Unit #: E0525 Wall newspaper, Sanidad [Health], undated (Item 11-0396)
  - Photo Unit #: E0526 Wall newspaper, undated (Item 11-0397)
  - Photo Unit #: E0529 Dr. Imek Bernstein, Dr. Mark Straus, Alexander Goldberg, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0398)
  - Photo Unit #: E0530 Murray Nemeroff and Alexander Goldberg, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0399)
  - Photo Unit #: E0531 Murray Nemeroff and Alexander Goldberg, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0400)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/19)
  - Photo Unit #: E0532 Jose Martinez Fernandez [?] and Miguel Estella Angel, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0401)
  - Photo Unit #: E0539 Antonio Gil Cabezas (Commissar, 59th Battalion), Captain German Hernandez (Commander, 59th Battalion), Captain Mark Millman (Adjuntant, 59th Battalion), Ebro Front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1502)
  - Photo Unit #: E0544 Plano Mayor, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0402)
  - Photo Unit #: E0545 Comrades in rain on railroad tracks, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0403)
  - Photo Unit #: E0546 Battalion activities, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0404)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/2)
  - Photo Unit #: E0547 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0405)
  - Photo Unit #: E0548 Lloyd (Red) Johnson [alias Joseph Shenker] and Ernest Kozlowsky, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0406)
  - Photo Unit #: E0549 Horseplay, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0407)
  - Photo Unit #: E0550 Lincoln-Washington group and girl from town, Darmos, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0408)
  - Photo Unit #: E0552 Ramon Sanchez, Samuel Romer and William Latham, Lincoln-Washington delegates to greet Unión General de Trabajadores and Confederación Nacional de Trabajo, May 1938 (Item 11-0409)
  - Photo Unit #: E0556 Topographers, 15th International Brigade, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0410)
  - Photo Unit #: E0557 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic addressing delegates and soldiers (Sanidad [Health], Vigilancia, Zapadores), Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0411)
  - Photo Unit #: E0561 Groups mentioned in #411, and Unión General de Trabajadores and Confederación Nacional de Trabajo delegates, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0412)
  - Photo Unit #: E0568 Unión General de Trabajadores and Confederación Nacional de Trabajo delegates and officers of 15th International Brigade, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0413)
  - Photo Unit #: E0571 Unión General de Trabajadores and Confederación Nacional de Trabajo delegates at 59th Battalion, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0414)
  - Photo Unit #: E0575 Delegate speaking, Unión General de Trabajadores and Confederación Nacional de Trabajo delegates at 59th Battalion, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0415)
  - Photo Unit #: E0580 John Gates addressing 59th Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0416)
  - Photo Unit #: E0581 John Gates presenting award to distinguished comrade, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0417)
  - Photo Unit #: E0585 May Day Unity wall newspaper, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0418)
  - Photo Unit #: E0586 May Day, Sanidad [Health], Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0419)
  - Photo Unit #: E0588 Commissar George Watt and new ambulance (American Student Union and Teachers), Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0420)
  - Photo Unit #: E0589 MacKenzie-Papineau kitchen, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-1503)
  - Photo Unit #: E0592 Our Planes! MacKenzie-Papineau Headquarters, Darmos [5 men looking toward sky], May 1938 (Item 11-1504)
  - Photo Unit #: E0593 Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0421)
  - Photo Unit #: E0594 Spanish section headquarters, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0422)
  - Photo Unit #: E0596 Lincoln-Washington Officers Aaron Lopoff, Milton Wolff, George Watt, Joseph Brandt, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0423)
  - Photo Unit #: E0597 Captain Leonard Lamb, Howard Goddard, Edwin Rolfe, Lincoln-Washington, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0424)
  - Photo Unit #: E0599 Transmiciones [Transmissions] class, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0425)
  - Photo Unit #: E0601 Training: Signal Corps (Transmiciones) class for Lincoln Brigade Members Darmos, 1937, May 1937 (Item 11-1505)
  - Photo Unit #: E0603 Transmiciones [Transmissions] group, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0426)
  - Photo Unit #: E0604 Transmiciones [Transmissions] group, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0427)
  - Photo Unit #: E0605 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, signs floated down river on May Day, Ebro, 1938 (Item 11-1867)
  - Photo Unit #: E0606 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, signs floated down river on May Day, Ebro ["Los Espanoles nunce seran esclavos del fascismo!"], May 1938 (Item 11-1506)
  - Photo Unit #: E0607 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, [3] signs floated down river on May Day, Ebro, May 1938 (Item 11-1507)
  - Photo Unit #: E0609 Sign floated down river on May Day, MacKenzie-Papineau 13th, Ebro Front, May 1938 (Item 11-1508)
  - Photo Unit #: E0610 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health] post, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-1509)
  - Photo Unit #: E0611 Water for the Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-1510)
  - Photo Unit #: E0620 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] wall newspaper, May 1938 (Item 11-0084)
  - Photo Unit #: E0628 Bob Lallemont, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0428)
  - Photo Unit #: E0632 Ebro Front, May 1938 (Item 11-0429)
  - Photo Unit #: E0633 Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0430)
  - Photo Unit #: E0634 Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-0431)
  - Photo Unit #: E0635 Lincoln-Washington Battalion presents awards to comrades, May 1938 (Item 11-0085)
  - Photo Unit #: E0637 Lincoln-Washington Battalion presents awards to comrades, May 1938 (Item 11-0086)
  - Photo Unit #: E0638 Lincoln-Washington Battalion May Day wall newspaper, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-1511)
  - Photo Unit #: E0639 Lincoln-Washington Battalion May Day wall newspaper, Darmos, May 1938 (Item 11-1512)
  - Photo Unit #: E0640 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0087)
  - Photo Unit #: E0645 [Soldier reading wall newspaper], May 1938 (Item 11-0432)
  - Photo Unit #: E0646 [Kitchen/preparing food], May 1938 (Item 11-0433)
  - Photo Unit #: E0647 [Kitchen/preparing food], undated (Item 11-0434)
  - Photo Unit #: E0648 [Woodworker, repairing (?)], undated (Item 11-0435)
  - Photo Unit #: E0649 [Soldiers, marching], undated (Item 11-0436)
  - Photo Unit #: E0650 [Soldiers at attention, inspection (?)], undated (Item 11-0437)
  - Photo Unit #: E0651 [Soldiers at attention, inspection (?)], undated (Item 11-0438)
  - Photo Unit #: E0652 [Soldiers at attention, inspection (?)], undated (Item 11-0439)
  - Photo Unit #: E0653 [Soldiers at attention, inspection (?)], undated (Item 11-0440)
  - Photo Unit #: E0654 [Soldiers at attention, inspection (?)], undated (Item 11-0441)
  - Photo Unit #: E0656 [Shooting range/target practice], undated (Item 11-0442)
  - Photo Unit #: E0657 Dr. Mark Straus and Dr. John Simon, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0443)
  - Photo Unit #: E0658 Dr. Mark Straus, Sanidad [Health], and Saul Wellman, Commissar of B Company, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0444)
  - Photo Unit #: E0660 [?], Dr. Julius Hene, Dr. Mark Straus, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0445)
  - Photo Unit #: E0661 Sanidad [Health] group, 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0446)
  - Photo Unit #: E0662 Sanidad [Health] officers, 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0447)
  - Photo Unit #: E0665 Group from 15th International Brigade at Valls Hospital, May 1938 (Item 11-1513)
  - Photo Unit #: E0666 Group from 15th International Brigade at Ulldemolins, May 1938 (Item 11-1514)
  - Photo Unit #: E0668 Scene in Ulldemolins, May 1938 (Item 11-1515)
  - Photo Unit #: E0676 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1516)
  - Photo Unit #: E0679 José María Varela (Assistant Commissar of 15th International Brigade), José María Sastre (Commissar of 35th Division) with 2 delegates from French Confederation Generale du Travail visiting 15th International Brigade, undated (Item 11-1517)
  - Photo Unit #: E0686 Frank Rogers, MacKenzie-Papineau Commissar, John Gates, 15th International Brigade Commissar, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1518)
  - Photo Unit #: E0687 Four MacKenzie-Papineau Lieutenants: Sanchez Rose [?], May 1938 (Item 11-0088)
  - Photo Unit #: E0689 Topographers, 15th International Brigade, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-0448)
  - Photo Unit #: E0698 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic visits MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1519)
  - Photo Unit #: E0702 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1520)
  - Photo Unit #: E0704 Festival, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1521)
  - Photo Unit #: E0705 MacKenzie-Papineau festival, May 1938 (Item 11-0089)
  - Photo Unit #: E0707 [? Addressing the troops], May 1938 (Item 11-0090)
  - Photo Unit #: E0710 Auto Park, Alcover, May 1938 (Item 11-1522)
  - Photo Unit #: E0711 Battalion delegates going to Activists Conference, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0091)
  - Photo Unit #: E0717 Activists conference, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0449)
  - Photo Unit #: E0725 Juventud Socialista Unificada Youth Congress, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1523)
  - Photo Unit #: E0726 David Gordon and Maurice Goldstein, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0450)
  - Photo Unit #: E0732 Barcelona delegates and 15th International Brigade men dancing, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1524)
  - Photo Unit #: E0733 Transmiciones [Transmissions] kitchen, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1525)
  - Photo Unit #: E0740 Some Canadians at lunch home, MacKenzie-Papineau, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1526)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative; Print; Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/52)
  - Photo Unit #: E0749 15th International Brigade officers at farewell to Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0451)
  - Photo Unit #: E0750 15th International Brigade officers at Valledor in Center, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0452)
  - Photo Unit #: E0752 Machine-Gunners Company, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0453)
  - Photo Unit #: E0753 Ole Swimmin Hole, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0454)
  - Photo Unit #: E0754 Ole Swimmin Hole, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0455)
  - Photo Unit #: E0755 Brigade Machine-Gunner Company, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0456)
  - Photo Unit #: E0756 Matti Mattson and Joseph Brandt, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0457)
  - Photo Unit #: E0762 Two from Lincoln Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0458)
  - Photo Unit #: E0767 Recruits training, Montblanch, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0459)
  - Photo Unit #: E0768 Recruits training, Montblanch, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0460)
  - Photo Unit #: E0771 Recruits training, Montblanch, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0461)
  - Photo Unit #: E0773 Lincoln Brigade members practice creeping and crawling, undated (Item 11-1527)
  - Photo Unit #: E0774 Recruits training, Montblanch, undated (Item 11-1528)
  - Photo Unit #: E0778 Recruits training, Montblanch, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0462)
  - Photo Unit #: E0779 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0463)